freebiespot.net 2014-03-28

# Freebie Spot Disclosure Policy and Privacy Policy | Freebie Spot

## Disclosure Policy

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. I believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for the posts or advertisements, I always give my honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the blogger’s own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

**Facebook Relationship**  
In order to comply with the latest [Facebook Promotion Guidelines](http://www.facebook.com/promotions_guidelines.php "Find out more") (revised 5/11/11), the following statements are true:

  * Giveaway participants release Facebook from any responsibility whatsoever.
  * Giveaways on this blog are in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with, Facebook.
  * Giveaway participants are providing information to this blog and giveaway sponsors only; not to Facebook.

**Changes to my Disclosure Policy**  
If I decide to change my disclosure policy, I will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Disclosure Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on May 12, 2011.

## Privacy Policy

**What information do I collect?**  
I collect information from you when you subscribe to my newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When commenting or registering on my site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit my site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on my site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to my users based on visits to my site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do I use your information for?**  
Any of the information I collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience: your information helps me to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve my website: I continually strive to improve my website offerings based on the information and feedback I receive from you.
  * To improve customer service: your information helps me to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do I protect your information?**  
I implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do I use cookies?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

I use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that I can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do I disclose any information to outside parties?**  
I do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist me in operating my website, conducting my business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. I may also release your information when I believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce site policies, or protect my or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at my discretion, I may include or offer third party products or services on my website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. I therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, I seek to protect the integrity of my site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because I value your privacy, I have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. I therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
I am in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). I do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. My website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**  
By using my site, you consent to my privacy policy.

**Changes to my Privacy Policy**  
If I decide to change my privacy policy, I will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on May 11, 2011.

## Contacting Me

If there are any questions regarding the disclosure policy or privacy policy, you may contact me at admin@freebiespot.net

About The Author

##  Jenny 

Hi there! I'm Jenny, a coffee-addicted, busy-body, work at home mom of two insane boys age 11 & 6\. I'm married to my best friend, obsessed with the Packers, and I love to cook, read, and design blogs (I'm kindof a geek). I love to hear from my readers so leave a comment below to join the conversation!
